KELSIE BLACKSTON

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Full stack web developer based in Indiana with skills in problem solving, communication, and graphic design. A naturally inquisitive, lifelong learner that's always open to new, innovative ideas and perspectives. Experience in using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Angular and SQL.

PROJECTS

MyFlix - React

Full Stack Development

- Server and client side movie application built with the MERN stack
- Users can register for accounts, view the movie list, and add movies to their favorites list

Meet App

Front-End Development

- A server less, progressive web application built with React
- Pulls information from a Google Calendar API
- Created using a test-driven development technique with Jest

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pricing Support Estimator

Deaconess Health System | October 2021 - Present

- Create pricing estimates for healthcare patients
- Answer patient inquiries via phone and email
- Use medical billing codes and diagnosis codes on daily basis to create estimates

Accounts Receivable Specialist

YMCA of Southern Indiana | May 2021 - Sept 2021

- Managed all YMCA childcare related billing and registration
- Managed terminations for YMCA members due to non-payment
- Updated excel spreadsheets for monthly AR tracking
- · Tracked childcare registration and billing for YMCA budgeting

Financial Care Advocate

Deaconess Health System | January 2020 - May 2021

- Followed up on missing registration from admission to hospital by visiting patient rooms and collecting information
- Notified of and/or collected any payments due
- · Presented and explained patient insurance benefits when necessary

CONTACT INFORMATION

270-823-7376

★ kelsieblackston@gmail.com

kblackston23

in kelsie-blackston23

Portfolio

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry

Web Development Certificate

September 2021 - May 2022

Murray State University

BS in Graphic Design

August 2013 - December 2016

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

Sass

React

Node.js

MongoDB

Express.js

NoSQL

Heroku

RESTful APIs

Jest

Test-Driven Development

React Native

Angular

Responsive Design

Adobe Creative Suite

GitHub/Git Version Control

SOFT SKILLS

Creativity

Problem Solving

Communication

Adaptability

Time Management

Resourcefulness

Teamwork

Critical Thinking